Let me introduce myself
You didn't think i was done
Did ya?
Well I just begun having my fun
Baby!
Some people live for attention
Playing the victim
But baby I was born to do the
Killing
I see how your going crazy
Always thinking bout me
Baby on the daily
Feed me your negativity
Talk some more about me
I know that you love me
Love me!
Monsters!!
I'm just being me
Cut out the things that I don't need
And I don't care if you disagree
I don't need no sympathy!!
Winning the game on my own
Yeah baby
I see how your going crazy
Always thinking bout me
Baby on the daily
Feed me your negativity
Talk some more about me
I know that you love me
Love me!
Monsters!!
Ah, it could've been so different between us
But then you went and messed everything up
You took a knife and stabbed me in the back
Took everything I had
Went to your friends and laughed
This is the last time
Imma gonna tell you now
If you try to break me
I'm gonna burn you down!
Baby I'm done with you
Not coming back for you
Monsters!!
KIRA - MONSTER (feat. GUMI)
Beatmap by Daycore, Shmiklak and Gordon123
Storyboard by Shmiklak
Hitsounded by Daycore